http://www.redandblack.com/site/privacy.html

Merch
Sweatshirts, tees and more!
Merch
Sweatshirts, tees and more!
Print issues
Copyright NoticeAll content on redandblack.com, including but not limited to text, graphics, photographs, design, code, archived material, whether generated by employees and staff of the site or by users, is copyrighted to The Red and Black Publishing Company, Inc. a non-profit Georgia corporation which owns this site.Our Commitment To PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.The Information We CollectThis notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the redandblack.com website. On some pages, you can create an account, make requests, participate in a poll, register for contests and submit content to the site. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name, email address, phone number, class standing, or affiliation within our online community. You may submit other types of personal information to fill out your optional profile.The Way We Use InformationIf you supply your email address, it will be used only for delivery of the newsletter, and will not be sold. Email subscribers have the option to opt in for occasional emails with special offers we  deliver on behalf of our partners, but we never share email information with second parties. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online or to verify identity for content they wish to be published on the site or in the printed editions of The Red and Black. Additionally, if you supply us with your postal address online you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.We use the information you provide about yourself when registering to identify you as a user of the site, to track usage of interactive features, and to communicate with you regarding site news and updates. Information we collect about users will be disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website. You can opt out of all newsletters, but you may still receive occasional notices regarding your specific usage of the site. We do not share this information with outside parties.We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our web site and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that "X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website," or that "Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form," but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.Our Commitment To Data SecurityTo prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.Third-Party AdvertisingWe and third parties may use cookies and other tracking technologies to facilitate serving relevant ads to you. For example, these technologies help determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before, tailor ads to you if you have visited our site before, and avoid sending you duplicate ads. You can learn more about certain types of targeted advertising by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance website. In addition to disabling cookies and other tracking technologies, you may opt-out of receiving targeted advertising from participating ad networks, audience segment providers, ad serving vendors, and other service providers by visiting websites such as this one operated by the Network Advertising Initiative.Our Commitment To Children's PrivacyProtecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.How You Can Access Or Correct Your InformationYou can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into your account and adjusting your account settings and profile information. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.How To Contact UsShould you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 706-433-3000 or send us an email to publisher@randb.com. Our postal address is The Red and Black, 540 Baxter St., Athens, GA 30605 ATTN: Rebecca Burns
© Copyright 2020 RedAndBlack.com, 540 Baxter St Athens, GA | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
